univariety.com 2016-04-12

# Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

### Introduction

Univariety.com is a product of International Education Gateway ('IEG') which is a Singapore based organization (Authroised collection agent for India - College Street Education Technologies Pvt. Ltd.) and believes in the necessity of Global exposure in today's higher education. With offices in Singapore, India and UK currently, IEG strives to work with institutions and students who believe in the power of Global Opportunities. Opportunities come in many shapes and sizes; there can be a large opportunity in accessing the "Best Fitting" university & course for the individual versus just going by some popular names which don't fit the needs. Or say, the face to face interactions at a young age with a learned professor from a foreign country can result in broadening of horizons for the student and result in opening up of many opportunities. At IEG, we believe that many gateways can be opened up if resources are pooled in hence we enable partnerships between like minded institutes around the world. 

### Use of Cookies

We use "cookie" technology and web server logs to collect information about how our web site is used by you. Cookies are small pieces of data that are stored by your web browser on your hard drive. The cookies allow our web servers to recognize the computer used by you to access our websites. Cookies allow you to move from page to page on the website, by remembering the information about the entire session.

Information gathered through cookies and by our web server logs may include the date and time of visits, your IP address, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. This information may be appended to your personal information provided by you to us to help us provide you with better service and information. It also may be collected on an aggregate basis, and shared with or collected by third-party Web analytics services to help International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. understands our users' aggregated Web site usage patterns and related trends

### Security

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. has security measures in place to help protect against the loss, misuse and/or unauthorized alteration of the information you provide to us or that we collect. You are the only user authorized to update your profile, unless you provide your password information to another party. We will assume that anyone who has the required login information and password for your account is you, so please keep this information confidential.

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. helps protect personally identifiable information by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the servers where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, are bound by confidentiality and our security procedures are reviewed and revised periodically.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. reserves the right to update this Privacy Policy from time to time without notice to users other than posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. After posting such amended Privacy Policy, all information provided to us will be subject to the terms of the amended Privacy Policy. Please visit this page periodically so that you will be apprised of any changes. Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Privacy Policy. 

### Information Sharing and Disclosure

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: 

  * We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd communicates with you about offers from International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. 
  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.
  * We transfer information about you if International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. 

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with the laws prevalent in Singapore to protect personal information about you. 

### Disclaimer

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. Provides information created both by International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd, and by third parties. While our site strives to provide accurate advice, International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. Does not make any warranty regarding the accuracy, reliability or use of any information provided on this site. 

### Your Consent

By using this Web site, you consent to the terms of our Online Privacy Policy and to International Education Gateway's processing of Personal Information for the purposes mentioned above.

### Contact Information

International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd. welcomes your comments regarding this privacy statement at the contact address given at the website. Should there be any concerns about contravention of this Privacy Policy, International Education Gateway Pte. Ltd will employ all commercially reasonable efforts to address the same.

International Education Gateway Pte Ltd © 2016 . All Rights Reserved . Univariety
